Long ago, there was a warrior.
In order to protect his friend,
the warrior had to take his friend's life.
Long ago, there was a sword.
This sword had continued to fight for peace,
yet realized that to protect the peace,
it had no choice but to kill the one who wielded it,
and thus took its master's life.
The warrior and the sword had to do what they did,
but was that really what they ought to have done?
Uncertain of the answer, even now,
they wander aimlessly.
Where are you, Muto?
There's nowhere else left for me to look.
Her again.
Persistent girl.
Fakir.
So you're awake.
Where's Tutu?
Don't worry.
Tutu is long gone.
What happened?
Tutu helped me.
She tried to restore part of my heart to me.
Muto, you know.
That's when Krayhi came.
Krayhi?
Yes.
She was dressed like a black bird and she took the peace.
Tell me, Fakir.
Wouldn't it...
Wouldn't it be better for me if I regained all the pieces of my heart?
Forget about it.
But...
Listen to me.
I brought you back here because I thought it would be safer to have people around.
Bury your worries in sleep.
What...
What is this?
Why?
Who's there?
Why did you bring me back with you?
Are you Muto's?
I...
I brought you with me?
What do you mean?
You want to know a lot, don't you?
I know how you feel.
Because I am the desire for knowledge.
Desire for knowledge?
You don't remember how you brought me here?
I brought you?
You're lying.
Why do you don black feathers?
No!
Do you have a special power dwelling within you?
Come on, tell me.
Which one is the real you?
Stop it!
Who are you really?
Stop!
You're lying!
I'm lying.
Why do you don black feathers?
Do you have a special power dwelling within you?
Come on, tell me, which one is the real you?
Stop it!
Who are you really?
Stop!
I saw you!
I saw you for sure!
Confessing your love in the window?
Duck, you're so bold!
What?
It was like a reverse Romeo and Juliet,
but horribly different in that it was so one-sided.
No, that's not it.
Muto disappeared and I...
Right!
I forgot!
He hasn't been to class in a long time, huh?
That's why you couldn't contain yourself and resolve to confess.
No, it isn't.
Take this chance to attack!
Attack!
Though you really have no hope
since the wonderful Muto already has room.
Go for it!
Take your losses!
Losing me, crush!
But I was just...
He might show up for class today.
What?
You think so?
You're hopeful, aren't you?
That's so cute!
Will Muto come today?
If he does, you have to say it loud and clear.
Huh?
Say what?
Oh, come on, Duck!
What else?
Huh?
That you love him!
What?
I can't tell him that!
Because...
Because if I said that, I'd vanish.
Oh, you can!
Oh, how are you going?
It was your fault!
Get away!
Oh!
Duck!
What are you doing?
Muto!
You're all right!
I'm so glad!
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry!
I looked all over town, but I couldn't find you, so I was wondering what happened to you, and
now seeing you're okay, it's such a relief, and I...
I'm just glad that you're okay.
You were looking for me?
Yeah!
Oh!
That's right!
He doesn't know I'm Tutu, so...
Huh?
Tutu?
Uh...
Do you know about Tutu, Duck?
Um...
What are you doing?
Ah!
Look here!
Muto.
You go ahead.
I'll be right there.
Yes.
Now you.
Ha!
Yes!
You're such an eyesore.
Listen carefully.
Never come near Muto again.
If you do, I'll make sure you pay for it.
Ha!
So, what was the outcome?
Does this mean she failed?
It was a rather subdued letdown, but we'll set a revenge match for her.
Uh-huh!
Last night, I saw Tutu return a piece of Muto's heart to him.
Muto also wished for its return.
Then...
I saw that...
And after that...
What...
Who...
Who am I?
What did it say?
It's very strange.
I've made my mind.
I skipped all my morning classes.
Fakir had that scary look in his eyes.
Muto shouldn't be with someone like that.
But what should I do?
Oh, hello, Miss Edo!
Masero?
Yes, hello, duck.
Masero, I need some help.
I want to save Mewto from Fakir,
but Fakir told me not to go near Mewto
or else he'd make me pay for it,
which kind of scares me, but, I mean, or rather...
Huh?
The name of this gem is Courage,
a single gem made of two.
A single gem made of two?
Does that mean I should work together with someone?
But who?
I can't put Ru in danger.
I want you to restore my heart, Tutu.
If... if I let Mewto know that I'm Tutu,
then together we might be able to stand up to Fakir.
Fakir?
What is Fakir to you, duck?
Huh? What is he?
Nothing really to me.
But he's a dangerous person to Mewto.
Oh!
What?
Miss Eero!
All right...
Miss Eero...
Maена...
So good!
Miss Eero...
Oh, no! Someone's coming!
An iguana?
That was close.
What?
There.
You're so stupid.
There's no way you were going to find any food in there.
I guess you wouldn't have wandered in if you knew.
You sure eat a lot.
Hurry home.
Don't come around anymore.
Somehow he wasn't like the usual fuck here.
If you do, I'll make sure you pay for it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He's definitely a bad guy.
I'm not going to be fooled just because the bread was tasty.
He probably acted like that only because I was just a duck.
A duck?
If I'm going to tell him you tell everything,
I better tell him that I'm just a duck too, shouldn't I?
What?
What's that?
Duck says she has something important to tell me.
I'll be waiting in the school's backyard at five o'clock this evening, duck.
Did that girl not hear what I said to her?
Throw it away. There's no need to go.
No.
What?
I've chosen to go. For Kier.
You're kidding, right?
I mean it.
What point is there?
Maybe there's something she can tell me about Tutu.
Who, duck?
Yes.
Moron. There's no way she could know.
But...
Don't get involved with Tutu.
Her existence will just bring you unhappiness in the end. Don't be fooled.
Huh?
And on top of that, you have that Krehie chasing after you right now.
I don't care.
If I tell you no, it's no! You got that?
No.
That's enough from you!
Oh my god, something!
I'm sorry.
I am going.
So I'm no longer able to stop Muto with words.
Let's go.
Uh-oh!
That is the prince's own sword, which once shattered his heart.
Now, what do you plan to do with it?
Ha ha ha...
Ha ha ha!
The sword, the heart of Princess has broken up,
and its proudissiveness of a physiotherapist have created it.
It's oraz tudo i ingrained!
Is and of all of you together!
To prove it!
The priest was in the heart of Princess Prattons and death so heavened,
has further heavy legislation.
Again, I.
Wher of the Bride.
So elevating us to give up this power,
Mewtwo!
Mewtwo...
Sigh...
Uh...
Uh...E-I-E-I...
Huh?
Oh...
Is that Duck?
Um...I...I...uh...
Actually...actually...
T-T-T-T-T-T...
Tutu...
Huh? No way!
You knew all along?
You know about Tutu, don't you, Duck?
Huh?
Oh...you scared me.
Fakir told me that I shouldn't come here, but...
You...told Fakir about this?
Yes.
Right!
Everything I tell Mewtwo goes straight to Fakir, too!
Duck...
Yes?
I...I want to see Tutu.
Huh?
Whenever I think of Tutu, I become filled with the desire to see her.
Mewtwo...
I want to be with Tutu always.
My prince, you belong to me.
Huh?
Crazy!
That's right!
That's the spirit!
The value of treasure is revealed when it's fought over!
Huh?
That's right!
The value of treasure is revealed when it's fought over!
Now, which deserving maid would the prince want to go to?
My dear princess Tutu,
My dear princess Tutu...
My Princess Tutu...
Wait!
My dear princess Tutu...
Your hair, your cheeks, even your heart, everything belongs to me.
Please stop, Cray-hee.
Princess Tutu.
Return the heart shard you took.
Stop making the prince suffer.
Tutu.
I'm trembling.
Look, my prince.
There's the one making you suffer, Princess Tutu.
What?
No!
No, that's a lie!
My poor prince.
I'm the one you need.
I alone.
I will always be with you.
Cray-hee.
You're like a doll, but I will love you.
I will make you forget Tutu.
We'll just give these heart things to the crows.
No!
That's the princess sword.
So, you're Cray-hee?
How dare you address me, Phil!
Are you the Raid of Manifest?
Who am I supposed to be?
The shard!
It's no use.
Huh?
Princess Tutu.
Who am I?
Fuck here!
Sorry you've had to wait, Muto.
It's all right now.
You won't have to suffer.
What are you doing?
Sit down.
I'll set things right.
I will shatter your heart for you once again.
What?
And you will not stop me, Princess Tutu!
Muto!
You, Bakir, you're the one who shattered Muto's heart.
Why'd you do such an awful thing?
If you had not shown up, then none of this would have happened.
I...
Tutu.
Fakir, stop it!
Priest!
Is it my fault?
If I pierce my heart with this sword, will that satisfy you, Fakir?
That's right.
Then you'll return to your old self.
All right.
Right.
Muto!
Don't do it!
You'd rather be without a heart?
Do it!
Quickly, pierce your heart!
Muto, please don't!
No!
Do it now!
Do it!
No!
The other day you smiled, remember?
When I saw that, I thought this must be the real you.
I believe if your heart is fully restored, then you'd be able to show even more of yourself.
Because that's the real you!
I'm sorry.
I can't save or protect you from the suffering.
Because all I can do is restore your heart to you.
That's it.
Muto!
I see.
So this is the answer you have chosen.
Tutu, restore this heart shard to me.
Princess Tutu, I want to know what do you think of me.
I want to know.
I...
Wait.
Tutu.
Why are you running?
I'm a duck.
I'm really only a bird.
But what the prince sees is Princess Tutu in her beautiful dress.
It's not me.
Was what the sword pierced the prince's heart?
Or was it someone's feelings?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha, ha ha ha ha!
I am Rue.
I'm not anyone else.
That's who I've always been.
Rue, maybe I'm actually...
Once again, Princess Tutu will change Mewtwo.
Cray-hee, why are you in such pain?
Be gone, you ugly crow.
That's right, I am a crow.
And I alone am the true prima donna, Princess Cray-hee.
All who love stories gather up.
эof.
You can't find all sorts of emails.
Do you likeuju circles?
Call poster.
Pls come here.
Josh, you can히 write andache in the process.
All right.
We'll beendeck right now.
Let's try nossas Ws.